### **ANGEL CAMARGO**

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER



adcamargo10@gmail.com



https://acamargoportfolio.netlify.app/



**B2 - ENGLISH LEVEL** 



https://www.linkedin.com/in/angel-camargo-942127241/



https://github.com/AngelCamargo4O4

### **ABOUT ME**

Graduated as an informatic engineer at Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin, having more than 6 years learning, and 4 years of demonstrable experience creating web apps, coding mainly in modern JavaScript, React Native, React.js, Node.js, SQL/NOSQL DBs, Tailwindcss, +7.0/+8.0. Laravel. Bootstrap, HTML and CSS, constantly learning. Great teamworker with an impeccable reputation as a programmer, experience working remotely.

## **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSIDAD RAFAEL BELLOSO CHACIN

Informatic Engineering, Aug 2018 - Nov 2022

### **UDEMY**

HTML, CSS JS PHP and Laravel Developer - MernStack Developer, and others. 2021 - 2023

## **EXPERIENCE**

HORNSTROMP STUDIO (CONTRACT/REMOTE) Fullstack Web Developer - Bulding, optimizing, and enhancing key features with popular APIs.

Jul 2024 - Present



- Integrated functionalities using APIs like YouTube and merged videos using FFmpeg.
- Suggested and implemented UI enhancements, such as new popups.
- · Identified and resolved production bugs.

#### SOUSTITREUR - CANADA (CONTRACT/REMOTE)

FullStack Web Developer - Proficient in building, optimizing, and troubleshooting key functionalities.

Aug 2023 - Jun 2024



- Migrating current functions of main project to secondary project and mobile app.
- Fixing bugs, sometimes finding them without any information about it.
- Updating functionalities and creating new important features they need for soustitreur and pluscrew projects.

BLUECARIBU - COLOMBIA (CONTRACT/REMOTE)

FullStack Web Developer creating multiple web projects

March 2023 - Jan 2024

bluecaribu

- I created an app from scratch using JavaScript (react, node, socket.io, mongodb, and more).
- I have created some new features and updated other functionalities previously built.
- I fixed some bugs debugging functions of the app.
- Fast learner and problem solver.

ALFA CO SAC - PERU (FREELANCE/REMOTE)
FullStack Web Developer creating JavaScript/PHP
app and other features
Jul 2020 - Sep 2023

- I made an API REST to make the connection between a mobile app and the database, using JavaScript/PHP.
- I created and deployed an administrative app from zero satisfying client needs using JavaScript/PHP.
- · Making new features and fixing bugs.
- I created the entire database from scratch using MySQL and connecting db and client with PHP and JavaScript.

## **SKILLS**

Advanced: JS - PHP - React.js - Node.js - NOSQL - SQL -

Nest.js - MongoDB - MySQL

Intermediate: Wordpress - Next.js - Express.js - Vue.js - React

Native - Laravel 9 - Heroku - HTML5 & CSS3

**Moderate:** AWS - Codeigniter 4 - Python - Socket.io